Earl Crabb collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Guides to the Collections in the Archive of Folk Culture
Earl Crabb collection 1953-2015
AFC 2016/048
Crabb, Earl, collector.
approximately 5076 items
55 sound tape reels: analog; 7 in.
5 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
1 sound tape reel: analog; 4 in.
1 sound tape reel: analog; 3 in.
1 sound cassette: analog.
approximately 2000 photographs: film, negatives, black and white, color and color transparencies; various sizes.
636 contact sheets: black and white.
11 binders of photographic prints: black and white; 8 x 10 in.
approximately 600 photographic prints, some matted: black and white, color; 4 in. x 5 in. to 20 in. x 24 in.
approximately 25 posters, drawings, and brush and ink artworks.
1 mini data cartridge (3M 2120)
1752 items.
Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Collection of photographs, audio recordings, ephemera, flyers, and programs which document the east and west coast folk and rock music scenes during the 1960s and 1970s including the Sky River Rock Festival, the Indian Neck Folk Festival, and various concerts. Photographs represent Earl Crabb's documentation of music events and his studio work. Earl Crabb photographed weight-lifting, fashion, album and magazine covers, circus performers, theater events, as well as people, markets, cities, and events in countries around the world. Ephemera includes flyers from folk clubs such as Cafe Yana in Boston, Massachusetts; Club 47 in Cambridge, Massachusetts; and the Freight and Salvage coffeehouse in Berkeley, California. Collection includes editions of Broadside magazine, Hootenanny, and the Philadelphia Folksong Society's Tune Up, which advertised these events. Of special interest are photographs from the Sky River Rock Festival, 1968-1970, in Washington State, and early editions of "Humbead's Revised Map of the World" produced in Berkeley, California. Sixty-two audio recordings in the collection, made during the 1960s and 1970s, include concert and coffeehouse performances by the Cleanliness and Godliness Skiffle Band, Wayne Smith and Ry Cooder, Tom Danaher, Dave and Megan Marash, Styx River Ferry, Hank Bradley, Ace Martel, Erik Frandsen, Jim and Jesse McReynolds; a recording of author Joseph Campbell, and others; some recordings are unidentified.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Bradley, Hank (Fiddler); Campbell, Joseph, 1904-1987; Cooder, Ry; Crabb, Earl, 1941-2015; Crabb, Earl, 1941-2015.; Danaher, Thomas J.; Frandsen, Erik, 1946-; Marash, Dave; Marash, Megan
Organizations
Cleanliness and Godliness Skiffle Band; Humbead Enterprises.; Jim and Jesse; Sky River Rock Festival.
Subjects
Coffeehouses--California--20th century.; Coffeehouses--Massachusetts--20th century.; Documentary photography.; Folk music festivals--Photographs.; Folk music--United States.; Folk musicians--Photographs.; Popular music,--1961-1970.; Rock music festivals--Washington (State)--Photographs.; Rock music--West (U.S.); Rock musicians--Photographs.
Places
Berkeley (Calif.)
Form/Genre
Concerts.; Correspondence.; Ephemera.; Photographs.; Posters.; Programs.; Sound recordings.
Arrangement
Organized by format into the following series: I. Manuscripts; II. Sound Recordings; III. Photographs; IV. Artifacts.
Acquisition
Cindy Crabb, Giselle Shepatin; 2016, 2017.
Access and Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Access to recordings may be restricted. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at http://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Biographical Notes
Earl Crabb, photographer, computer programmer, entrepreneur. He designed on-line-banking programs for Bank of America, the first touch screen program for a Canadian tourist bureau, bank security, and investment software for financial institutions. He was involved in the 1960s traditional and folk music scene as a producer, photographer, and organizer. From 1968 until his death, he was owner of Humbead Enterprises, creating and publishing posters (including, with Rick Shubb, "Humbead's Revised Map of the World," "El Hashish," and "Enantiodromia"). In addition he worked as an actor, an artist (under a pseudonym), and as a sound engineer, claiming to be the first person to record Bob Dylan in front of an audience. He provided support to such artistic endeavors as the San Francisco Mime Troupe and the Pickle Family Circle, as well as other performers and artists. He majored in economics at Williams College from 1959-1964. Born September 6, 1941 in Le Sueur, Minnesota; he died February 20, 2015 in San Francisco, California.
Scope and Content
Collection of photographs, audio recordings, ephemera, flyers, and programs which document the east and west coast folk and rock music scenes during the 1960s and 1970s including the Sky River Rock Festival, the Indian Neck Folk Festival, and various concerts. Photographs represent Earl Crabb's documentation of music events and his studio work. Earl Crabb photographed weight-lifting, fashion, album and magazine covers, circus performers, theater events, as well as people, markets, cities, and events in countries around the world. Ephemera includes flyers from folk clubs such as Cafe Yana in Boston, Massachusetts; Club 47 in Cambridge, Massachusetts; and the Freight and Salvage coffeehouse in Berkeley, California. Collection includes editions of Broadside magazine, Hootenanny, and the Philadelphia Folksong Society's Tune Up, which advertised these events. Of special interest are photographs from the Sky River Rock Festival, 1968-1970, in Washington State, and early editions of "Humbead's Revised Map of the World" produced in Berkeley, California. Sixty-two audio recordings in the collection, made during the 1960s and 1970s, include concert and coffeehouse performances by the Cleanliness and Godliness Skiffle Band, Wayne Smith and Ry Cooder, Tom Danaher, Dave and Megan Marash, Styx River Ferry, Hank Bradley, Ace Martel, Erik Frandsen, Jim and Jesse McReynolds; a recording of author Joseph Campbell, and others; some recordings are unidentified.
Container List
- Series I: Manuscripts
  - Correspondence and contacts, 1964-2000 (Box-folder 1/1)
    Each item or group of items (materials from one envelope) is housed in a separate bond paper folder. Materials include correspondence sent to Earl Crabb, ranging from generic event reminders to a postcard from Tandy Beal (for 10 years the artistic director of the Pickle Family Circus), a handwritten letter from "Mac" (probably Mac Wiseman), a handwritten letter from Mary DuShane (the original fiddler with the Powdermilk Biscuit Band, which played on the "Prairie Home Companion" radio show), and a handwritten contact list of names and phone numbers for various individuals (including Jim Kweskin, Jack Elliott, John Hammond, and others).
  - Preliminary drawings and lists for "Humbead's Revised Map of the World," 1967-1968 (Box-folder 1/2)
    Envelope with drawings and legal instructions regarding intellectual rights.
  - Recording contract, October 5, 1967, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/3)
    Contract between Vanguard records and the Cleanliness and Godliness Skiffle Band.
  - Flyers, calendars, and programs (originals), folder 1 of 2, 1960s-1970s, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/4)
    Individual events such as the annual fiddlers's conventions in Berkeley, event calendars for Freight and Salvage, and programs for events such as the Concert of Folk Music, presented by the Williams Motorcycle Club, and flyers for groups, such as the San Francisco Mime Troupe, and for clubs on both U.S. coasts such as Café Yana, Moon-Cussler, Golden Vanity, and Club 47.
  - Flyers, calendars, and programs (originals), folder 2 of 2, 1960s-1970s, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/5)
    See notes for folder 1/4.
  - Flyers and calendars (photocopies), 1 folder (Box-folder 1/6)
    Photocopies sent to Earl Crabb, with notes.
  - Printed and handwritten documents, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/7)
    A few pages of handwritten notes, and for the most part printed documents such as lyrics, a backstage pass for the 1967 Berkeley Folk Music Festival, informational flyers, a printout of Pete Frame's Berkeley music "family tree" (replacing a photocopied and taped version that arrived with the collection), programs for the memorial tribute to Earl Crabb, newspaper and magazine clippings, and related materials.
  - Manuscript materials from sound recording containers, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Manuscript materials from photo albums, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/2)
    Items delivered with photographic materials but with no direct association to them. Includes a fragmented flyer for Club 47, Inc., business cards (including one for Earl Crabb, from E/Soft), and two copies of "Humbead's Revised Map of the World" (8 in. x 10 in. and 5 3/4 in. 7 1/4 in.).
  - Song lists for sound recordings (folder 1 of 4), 1960s-1990s, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/3)
    Various versions and degrees of completion for a list of sound recordings in the collection. A few pages are handwritten, and the rest typed, dittoed, or printed from a computer document. According to one set of lists dated 1998, the recordings were "recently" found in the attic, assumed to be Earl Crabb's home.
  - Song lists for sound recordings (folder 2 of 4), 1960s-1990s, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/4)
    See notes for folder 2/2.
  - Song lists for sound recordings (folder 3 of 4), 1960s-1990s, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Song lists for sound recordings (folder 4 of 4), 1960s-1990s, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Broadside, 1962-1964, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/7)
    Magazine issue numbers 5, 33, 40, and 45, and one unnumbered compilation issue.
  - The Broadside, vol. II, 1963, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/8)
    Magazine issue numbers 8 (two copies), 9, 10, 13 (cover only), 15, 18, 19, 23, and 20. Some issues are incomplete.
  - The Broadside vol. III, 1964-1965, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/9)
    Magazine issue numbers 1-8 (two copies of issue 2), 14-15, 17-19, and 22-25.
  - The Broadside, vol. IV, 1965, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/10)
    Magazine issue numbers 1-3, 5-6, 8-9.
  - Hootenanny, 1963-1964, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/1)
    4 magazine issues; not all are complete.
  - Tune Up, 1963-1964, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/2)
    Magazine issues vol. 2, no 1; vol. 2, no. 2; October 1964, and November 1964.
  - Rolling Blunder Review, 1987-1989, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/3)
    Magazine issue numbers 5 and 9-12.
  - Periodicals (folder 1 of 2), 1960-1990s, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/4)
    Periodicals covering music industry and business subjects, with some of general interest.
  - Periodicals (folder 2 of 2), 1960-1990s, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/5)
    See note for folder 3/5.
  - Catalogs, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/6)
    A catalog for County Records and Publications, and a catalog from the store Archie McPhee.
- Series II: Sound recordings
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival. Original ID number: 1, May 6, 1961, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR01)
  - Left Bank shows, Indian Neck Folk Festival (1961), and dubs of commercial recordings. Original ID number: 4, circa 1961, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR02)
  - Williams Motorcycle Club concert, at Adams Memorial Theatre, Williamstown, MA. Original ID number: 6, November 10, 1962, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog, 4 track, stereo; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR03)
  - Original ID number: 7, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR04)
  - Original ID number: 10, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR05)
  - Dubs of commercial recordings. Original ID number: 11, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR06)
  - Original ID number: 12, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR07)
  - Original ID number: 13, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR08)
  - Original ID number: 17, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR09)
  - Some dubs of commercial recordings, and some that may be original. Original ID number: 23, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR10)
  - Dubs of commercial recordings. Original ID number: 28, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR11)
  - Original ID number: 30, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR12)
  - Original ID number: 44 on reel, 70 on tape box, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR13)
  - Original ID number: 60 on reel, 61 on tape box, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR14)
  - David and Megan Marash. Original ID number: 60, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR15)
  - Original ID number: 71, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR16)
  - "Farinas" written on tape reel; probably Richard and Mimi Fariña. "Skiffle Band Earl's Crab Joint" written on tape reel; probably Cleanliness and Godliness Skiffle Band, performing at Earl's Crab Joint. Original ID number: 72, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR17)
  - Original ID number: 75, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR18)
  - Original ID number: 100, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR19)
  - Original ID number: 101, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR20)
  - Original ID number: 102, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR21)
  - Original ID number: 104, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR22)
  - Original ID number: 110, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR23)
  - Cleanliness and Godliness Skiffle Band, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR24)
  - Cleanliness and Godliness Skiffle Band, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR25)
  - Cleanliness and Godliness Skiffle Band; possibly a radio broadcast, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 3 1/4 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR26)
  - Cleanliness and Godliness Skiffle Band; possibly recorded in Berkeley, California in the 1960s, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR27)
  - Wayne Smith and Ry Cooder, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR28)
  - Wilson, Shubb, and Shubb, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog, 7 1/2 ips, 1/4 track, stereo; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR29)
  - Tom Danaher, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR30)
  - Dave and Megan Marash, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 4 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR31)
    - Relax Your Mind
    - My World Is Dust
    - Cow Cow Yickey
  - Odds and ends, 1 sound tape reel (polyester and acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR32)
  - Interviews: Grand Ole Opry, Nashville, 1976, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR33)
  - Fiddle lesson 1) Richard Green 2) Peter Stampfel (of Holy Modal Rounders), 1 sound tape reel (polyester and acetate): analog 7 1/2 ips (part 1), 3 3/4 ips (part 2); 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR34)
  - Styx River Ferry [band], in concert at Freight and Salvage 1968-1970, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR35)
  - Hank Bradley, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR36)
  - Hank Bradley - banjo pieces. Philco Radio Time, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR37)
  - Philco Radio Time, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR38)
  - Arlo Guthrie, "Crevasse", 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR39)
  - Dynamite Annie Johnston and guitar. Johnston played with the Cleanliness and Godliness Skiffle Band, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR40)
  - Zason C., 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR41)
  - Ace Martel, tape 1, 1977, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR42)
  - Ace Martel, tape 2, 1977, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR43)
  - Various recordings, circa 1953-1962, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR44)
    - Martin and Lewis in a studio while recording publicity releases for one of their pictures entitled "The Caddy" (circa 1953)
    - Wally Cox yodeling backwards
    - Frank Ifield, "I Remember You" (circa 1962)
    - Annie Master (continued on Side 2)
  - Mark S. and Paul Hecht, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR45)
  - Campbell [?] - end on 1L, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR46)
  - Joseph Campbell: "Myths of Alienation and Rapture," at the Esalen Institute, 1970, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR47)
  - Jerry Foster, Lloyd Williams, Butch Waller at Sandy Rothman's house, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR48)
  - Unidentified recording, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR49)
  - Erik Frandsen, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR50)
  - Erik Frandsen #2, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR51)
  - Unidentified recording, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR52)
  - Branford 2:1, 1961, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR53)
  - 1L: Jim and Jesse McReynolds. 1R: Jimmy Martin, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR54)
  - Steve Mann, 1969, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR55)
  - Hopeless Fore; Sakar Marsh, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR56)
  - John Sl[??], May 10, 1970, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR57)
  - Dub of commercially-released Dylan Thomas recordings, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR58)
  - Unidentified recording, 1 sound tape reel (polyester): analog; 5 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR59)
  - Dave and Megan Marash, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR60)
    - Dr. Jazz
    - J.C. Holmes Blues
    - Sweet Mary Blues
    - Cow Cow Yickey
    - Relax Your Mind
  - Unidentified recording, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR61)
  - Unidentified recording, 1 sound tape reel (acetate): analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2016/048: SR62)
- Series III: Graphic materials
  - Subseries A: Photographic materials
    - Sub-subseries 1: Negatives
      - Black-and-white negatives, circa 1960s, 2 boxes (Boxes 4-5)
        366 35mm negative strips, with a few strips of 120mm negatives, 136 4 in. x 5 in. frames, and 9 individual frames measuring approximately 2 1/2 in. x 3 1/2 in. The individual images were originally housed in the pressed paper box (see the Artifact series for more details). The black and white positive of "Humbead's Revised Map of the World" is accompanied by paper prints of the same image.
      - Color negatives and positives, 1 box (Box 6)
        28 35mm color negative strips and 13 4 in. x 5 in. color positives, 9 of which are versions of the image that ultimately was used for the El Hashish poster.
    - Sub-subseries 2: Contact sheets and prints, 3 boxes (Boxes 7-9)
      636 contact sheets; all but one are black and white. Almost all contact sheets are for 35mm film, with a few examples of 120mm, 4 in. x 5 in., and various other sizes. The prints measure 8 in. x 10 in.
    - Sub-subseries 3: Prints (from binders), 4 boxes (Boxes 10-13)
      359 prints received in binders. They have been rehoused in their original order within each box. All but one are unmatted. The prints range in size from 4 in. x 6 in. to 8 in. x 10 in. (the latter size represents the majority of prints).
    - Sub-subseries 4: Prints (unmatted, loose), 3 boxes (Boxes 14-16)
      These prints were received from the donor loose and ungrouped. 152 prints; only a few are in color (in Box 16: 19 4 in. x 6 in. and one approximately 8 in. x 11 in.).
    - Sub-subseries 5: Large prints (matted and unmatted), 2 boxes (Boxes 17-18)
      109 prints; most are affixed to rigid paper mounts. All but one of the 24 unmounted prints are black and white. 5 mounted prints are in color. The items range in size from a 6 1/4 in. x 10 in. print affixed to a 7 3/4 in. x 10 in. mat, to a 7 in x 9 1/2 in. print affixed to a 10 1/2 in. x 15 in. mat. All unmounted prints are 11 in. x 14 in.
  - Subseries B: Graphic and photographic materials (oversize)
    - Flyers (Box-folder 19/1)
      4 flyers. Two copies of a Moon-Cusser Coffee House concert flyer (Ramblin' Jack Elliott and the Charles River Valley Boys; 9 1/2 in. x 12 1/2 in.), a flyer advertising Lester Flatt and Earl Scruggs and the Foggy Mountain Boys (9 in. x 10 1/2 in.), and an announcement (in color) for a production of "Three Penny Opera," staged at Adams Memorial Theatre (6 1/4 in. x 26 1/2 in.).
    - Posters (Box-folder 19/2)
      13 small posters printed on cardboard (multiple copies of some items). Announcements for events sponsored by the Williams Motorcycle Club (which Crabb helped to start), a concert to raise money for the March on Washington, and other music events. Items range in size from 11 in. x 14 in. to 14 in. x 22 in.
    - Publications, circa 1970s (Box-folder 19/3)
      Two issues of Earth Times (April 1970 and May 1970), a foldout newsprint publication with information about the 1970 Sky River Rock Festival, and other publications.
    - Unmatted photos (Box-folder 19/4)
      23 black and white photos; 16 in. x 20 in. Includes duplicates for almost all photos in this folder.
    - Matted photos (Box-folder 19/5)
      Three large-format photos on rigid supports (two portraits of individuals and one photo of a general store interior). Sizes range from 12 1/2 in. x 18 in. to 15 in. x 19 1/4 in.
    - Posters, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 19/6)
      Three copies each of the 1969 and the 1970 versions of "Humbead's Revised Map of the World," two copies of the Enantiodromia poster, with Jim Bamford's image (copyright 1969), and 2 copies of the El Hashish poster (copyright 1970). Measurements range from 17 in. x 22 in. to 17 1/2 in. x 23 in.
    - Berkeley 80's circa 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 19/7)
      Spreadsheet in black marker on paper with a workflow intended to the make fun of the process of gauging the probability of an event. The spreadsheet was updated at some point from the 1970s to the 1970s (in various places on the item). Item is oblong, measuring 12 1/4 in. x 40 in.
    - Oversize items (printed) 1962; undated (Box-folder 19/8)
      A small poster of a painting of Dave Fredrickson, by Carl Kasten (circa 1962), and a bumper sticker with the phrase, "Campbell Coe is a myth."
    - Subseries C: Art works (Box-folder 20/1)
      2 brush and ink art works, unframed.
- Series IV: Artifacts (Box 20)
  - Paper box, AFC 2016/048: AR01 (Box 20)
    One multicolored, pressed paper box with a detachable lid. The lid has a raised image of a dolphin.
  - Binder, AFC 2016/048: AR02 (Box 20)
    3-ring binder with the logo of E/Soft, a software company started by Earl Crabb.
  - Tape box for AFC 2016/048: SR22, AFC 2016/048: AR03 (Box 20)
    Tape box kept as an example of the original sound recording containers.